Guide to the Annina Nosei Gallery Archive 1963-2009 MSS.298
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Transaction Records, 1976-2006; 200731
  - Subseries G: Acquisition Receipts, 204151
    - C, 1983-1989; 206741 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - D, 1981-1984, 1989; 206742 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - F, 1984-1988; 206743 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - G, 1980-1989; 206744 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - H, 1979-1982, 1987; 206745 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - J, 1983-1989; 206747 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - K, 1982-1989; 206748 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - L, 1979, 1982, 1986-1989; 206749 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - M, 1982-1989; 206750 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Mc, 1988-1989; 206751 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - N, 1982-1987; 206752 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - O, 1982,1984; 206753 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - P, 1982-1988; 206754 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - R, 1983-1985; 206755 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - S, 1982-1989; 206756 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - T, 1979-1989; 206757 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - W, 1979, 1985-1989; 206758 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - YZ, 1979, 1986; 206759 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Subseries H: Invoices, 204152
    Subseries is arranged chronologically.
    Series comprises invoices for works sold by the gallery. Invoices [contain] inventory numbers and invoice numbers that can be matched with those found in Series I, Subseries A, B, E, and F. The final folder in this series, ["Gallery Policies"], while not an invoice, was originally filed with the invoices, so has remained in this series.
    - Invoices: Paid in Full 79, 1977-1980; 206898 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 4/24/81-2/25/82 (INvoice #195-330) [1/3] [Material from front pocket of binder], undated; 206899 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 4/24/81-2/25/82 (INvoice #195-330) [2/3], undated; 206900 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 4/24/81-2/25/82 (INvoice #195-330) [3/3], 1981-1982; 206901 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 11/5/82-12/27/83 (invoice 444-640) [1/2], 1982-1983; 206902 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 11/5/82-12/27/83 (invoice 444-640) [2/2], 1982-1983; 206903 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 12/28/83-12/31/84 (Invoice 641-807) [1/3], 1983-1984; 206904 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 12/28/83-12/31/84 (Invoice 641-807) [2/3], 1983-1984; 206905 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 12/28/83-12/31/84 (Invoice 641-807) [3/3], 1983-1984; 206906 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Invoices #808-978 1985 Paid [1/4], 206907 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Invoices #808-978 1985 Paid [2/4], 206908 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Invoices #808-978 1985 Paid [3/4], 206909 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Invoices #808-978 1985 Paid [4/4], 206910 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Invoices; 1986; 1987; 979 thru 1191 [1/4] [Note taped to inside of front flap of binder], 206911 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Invoices; 1986; 1987; 979 thru 1191 [2/4], 206912 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Invoices; 1986; 1987; 979 thru 1191 [3/4], 206913 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Invoices; 1986; 1987; 979 thru 1191 [4/4], 206914 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Current Invoices Nov. 1987; Dec. 1989; Compl. [1/3], 206915 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Current Invoices Nov. 1987; Dec. 1989; Compl. [2/3], 206916 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Current Invoices Nov. 1987; Dec. 1989; Compl. [3/3], 206917 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Paid Invoices #1610-1443; 1992 [1/2], 1990-1991; 206918 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Paid Invoices #1610-1443; 1992 [2/2], 1989-1990; 206919 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Paid Invoices #1717-1611; 1991 [1/2], 206920 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Paid Invoices #1717-1611; 1991 [2/2], 206921 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Paid Invoices 1993-1995 [1/5], 206922 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Paid Invoices 1993-1995 [2/5], 206923 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Paid Invoices 1993-1995 [3/5], 206924 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Paid Invoices 1993-1995 [4/5], 206925 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Paid Invoices 1993-1995 [5/5], 206926 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Paid Invoices - Jan. 1996; Begin Invoice #1921 [1/2], 1996-1997; 206927 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Paid Invoices - Jan. 1996; Begin Invoice #1921 [2/2], 206928 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Paid Invoices; 1997-1999; 2041-2207 [1/2], 1996-1999; 206929 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Paid Invoices; 1997-1999; 2041-2207 [2/2], 206930 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Paid Invoices #2252-2442; 11/00-12/04; 2000-12/2004 [1/6], 2003-2004; 206931 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Paid Invoices #2252-2442; 11/00-12/04; 2000-12/2004 [2/6], 2002-2003; 206932 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Paid Invoices #2252-2442; 11/00-12/04; 2000-12/2004 [3/6], 2001-2002; 206933 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Paid Invoices #2252-2442; 11/00-12/04; 2000-12/2004 [4/6], 2000-2001; 206934 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Paid Invoices #2252-2442; 11/00-12/04; 2000-12/2004 [5/6], 206935 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Paid Invoices #2252-2442; 11/00-12/04; 2000-12/2004 [6/6], undated; 206936 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - ["Gallery Policies"], undated; 206937 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Subseries I: Shipment Records, 204153
    Series comprises shipping forms for artworks shipped.
    - Shipping Forms Jan.00-Feb '01 [1/3], 2000-2001; 206942 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Shipping Forms Jan.00-Feb '01 [2/3], 2000-2001; 206943 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Shipping Forms Jan.00-Feb '01 [3/3] [Material from back pocket of binder], 2000-2001; 206944 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - "Shipment Record Book", undated; 206945 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Subseries J: Accounting, 204154
    Series comprises ten-column ledger sheets listing such information as buyer, date of sale, inventory and invoice numbers, price of the work, artist's commision, price of frame, and tax. Material in this subseries was originally in one of two binders. A General Note accompanying each folder description indicates to which of the two binders the contents belong.
    - [Unlabeled tab from Black Accounting Book], 1981-1987; 206946 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      From Black Accounting Book
    - Sales 10/80-10/83, 1981-1987; 206947 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Cash Receipts 11/80-4/83, 1980-1983; 206948 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Cash Receipts 5/83-4/84, 1983-1987; 206949 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Cash Disbursements 11/80-4/82, 1980-1982; 206950 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Cash Disbursements 5/82-4/83, 1982-1983; 206951 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Cash Disbursements 5/83-4/84, 1983-1984; 206952 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Cash Disbursements 5/84-4/85 [1/3], 1984-1985; 206761 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Cash Disbursements 5/84-4/85 [2/3], 1985-1986; 206760 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Cash Disbursements 5/84-4/85 [3/3], 1986-1987; 206763 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - [Inside Cover of Blue Accounting Binder], undated; 206764 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      From Blue Accounting Book
    - Artists Accts, 1992-1996; 206765 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Cash Received, 1993-1996; 206766 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Disbursements [1/2], 1993-1994; 206767 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Disbursements [2/2], 1994-1996; 206768 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Money Mkt/CDs; Disbursements/Recs, 1994-1995; 206769 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Series II: Correspondence, 1973-2008; 200735
  Series comprises correspondence sent and received by the Annina Nosei Gallery.
  The subseries reflect the gallery's original arrangement by sender/recipient.
  - Subseries A: Collectors, 204156
    Original arrangement alphabetical by sender/receiver original folder titles
    Series comprises correspondence between the gallery and individual art collectors, as well as other related documents.
    - A [1/2], 1980-1991; 206953 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - A [2/2], 1982-1993; 206954 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Jonathan Abrams, 1984-1989; 206955 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Ara Arslanian, 1980-1982; 206956 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - B [1] [1/2], 1995-2004; 206957 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - B [1] [2/2], 1990-1995; 206958 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - B [2] [1/2], 1981-2004; 206959 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - B [2] [2/2], 1981-1995; 206960 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Berezdivin, 1993-1998; 206961 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Budzein, 1991-1998; 206962 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Eugenio Borroni, 1990-1992; 206963 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - David Bermant, 1978, 1983; 206964 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Carlo Billotti, 1979-1980, 1987-1989; 206965 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Maggie and Edo Bult, 1981-1987; 206966 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Laura Blocker, 1984; 206967 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Eli Broad, 1981-2005; 206968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - C, 1996-2002; 206969 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Calabresi, 2000-2005; 206970 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Chase Manhattan, 1984-1989; 206971 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - De La Cruz Shipping, 1992; 206972 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Caduro, 1982-1987; 206973 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Dr. Bob Calle, 1982-1986; 206974 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Phoebe Chason, 1981-1983; 206975 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Cohn, 1983-1985; 206976 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Arthur Cohen, 1983-1998; 206977 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Peter Cover, 1985-1986; 206978 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Doiuglas Cramer, 1982-1983; 206979 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - D'Alessandro, 1986-1993; 206980 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Elaine Dannhesser, 1982-1985; 206981 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Charles Debordeau, 1983-1996; 206982 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Kiwi De Voy, 1984-1989; 206983 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Alan Dinsfriend, 1988-1990; 206984 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Diamond, 2001; 206985 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - D [1/2], 1979-2002; 206986 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - D [2/2], 1980-1989; 206987 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Jim Droment, 1981-1996; 206988 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - E [1/2], 1981-1999; 206989 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - E [2/2], 1980-1991; 206990 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Asher Edelman, 1982-1992; 206991 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - F [1/2], 1983-2001; 206993 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - F [2/2], 1982-1991; 206994 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Howard & Suzanne Feldman, 1981-1988; 206995 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Henry Friedman, 1982-1986; 206996 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - [Bonanni], 2003; 206998 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Golinelli/Pavirani [1/2], 1998-2003; 206999 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Golinelli/Pavirani [2/2], 1997-2005; 207000 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Pavirani Golinelli, 2007; 207001 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - G [1/3], 1992-2001; 207002 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - G [2/3], 1983-1994; 207003 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - G [3/3], 1981-1990; 207004 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Elaine Ganz, 1987-2010; 207005 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Carol & Arthur Goldberg, 1980-1995; 207006 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Janet Green, 1982-1992; 207007 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Bobby Heller, 1981-1984; 207008 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Hellman Holland, 1983-1989; 207009 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Doris & Robert Hillman, 1980-1982; 207010 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Robert & Margo Hirsch, 1983; 207011 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Camille & Paul Hoffman, 1987-1998; 207012 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Blanche Gutstein, 1980-1987; 207013 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - [Legal documents in case against Annina Nosei Gallery brough by Darius Glowacki], 1985; 207014 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - H [1/3], 1994-2003; 207015 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - H [2/3], 1982-1993; 207016 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - H [3/3], 19892-1991; 207017 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - I/J [1/2], 1982-2002; 207020 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - I/J [2/2], 1981-1990; 207021 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Aron Katz, 1981-1987; 207022 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Robert Kaye, 1983-1988; 207023 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Nicole Klagsburn, 1983-1984; 207024 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Jeffrey Kerns, 1985-1990; 207025 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Robert & Jill Kleiman, 1981-1983; 207026 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Peter L. Kellner, 2004; 207027 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Jean-Fraincois Lemoine, 1981-1994; 207028 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - [Vera List], 1982-19898; 207029 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Jacques & Delores Leviant, 1980-1984; 207030 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Sidney Lewis, 1982-1989; 207031 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - L [1] [1/3], 1988-2001; 207032 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - L [1] [2/3], 1978-1990; 207033 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - L [1] [3/3], 1973-1990; 207034 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Jim Lodge, 1982-1986; 207035 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - K [1/2], 1985-2003; 207036 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - K [2/2], 1982-1989; 207037 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Rama Linz, 2003-2004; 207038 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - L [2], 1982-2010; 207039 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Emilio Mazzoli, 2004; 207081 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Beverly Malen, 1998; 207040 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Lewis and Susan Manilow, 1981-1987; 207041 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Marsh & Allan May, 1981-1992; 207042 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Mc Crory Corporation, 1985-1988; 207043 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Marvin Mordes MD., 1985-1988; 207044 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Carlo Frua/Marco Noire [1/2], 1996-1998; 207045 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Carlo Frua/Marco Noire [2/2], 1996-1998; 207046 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Ron Margolis, 1996-2001; 207047 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - M [1] [1/3], 1987-1994; 207048 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - M [1] [2/3], 1982-1989; 207049 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - M [1] [3/3], 1980-1991; 207050 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - M [2], 1996-2001; 207051 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Sabina Melesi, 1997; 207052 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Mobil Oil, 1986; 207053 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - [Barry Morrison], 1982-1988; 207054 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Ray Nasher, 1996-2003; 207055 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Vernon Nikkel, 1981-1999; 207056 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Morton Newman, 1982-1985; 207057 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Andrew Nicoletta, 1981-1983; 207058 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - [O], 1994-1998; 207059 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Edwared & Barbara Okin, 1984-1986; 207060 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Omura, 1981-1989; 207061 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Seiji Nagai, 1997; 207062 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Norton, 2001-2005; 207063 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - O, 1999-2001; 207064 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Rafael Pereira, 1991-1992; 207065 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Jean Pigozzi, 1990-1999; 207067 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Alfonso Pons [1/2], 1991-1997; 207066 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Alfonso Pons [2/2], 1990-1991; 207068 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Robert [Ingmar] Pousette, 1990-2001; 207069 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Francesco Pelizzi [1/3], 1983-1989; 207070 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Francesco Pelizzi [2/3], 1979-1982; 207071 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Francesco Pelizzi [3/3], 1977-1979; 207072 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Raymond S. Page, 1981-1985; 207073 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Lois Plehn, 1980-1985; 207074 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Luis Pastore, 1982; 207075 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - P/Q [1/3], 1995-2002; 207076 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - P/Q [2/3], 1981-1995; 207077 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - P/Q [3/3], 1980-1989; 207078 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Fredrik Roos, 1981-1991; 207079 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Ed Robbins, 1982-1998; 207080 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Ring, 1984-1986; 207082 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Rosen, 1981-1985; 207083 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Rosenberg, 1982-1987; 207084 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - William Roth, 1983; 207085 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Bob Rowan, 1982-1991; 207086 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Selma Ruben, 1982-1990; 207087 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Rubell, 1981-1988; 207088 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Zanin, 2008-2009; 207089 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Lenore & Herbert Schorr, 1981-1994; 207090 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - S [1], 1988-2002; 207091 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Diego Sada, 1988-1993; 207092 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Steve Schapiro, 1985; 207093 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Martin Sanders, 1981-1991; 207094 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Charles [Saatchi], 1980-1989; 207095 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Thomas S. Schultz, 1983-1987; 207096 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Phil Schrager, 1982-1994; 207097 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Robert Shimshak, 1989; 207098 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Martin Sklar, 1983-1989; 207099 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Robert Sosnick, 1986-1988; 207100 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Emily Spiegel, 1982-1998; 207101 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Lynne Stacker, 1984-1989; 207102 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Arnold Steinberg, 1986; 207103 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Edwin L. Stringer, Q.C., 1982-1987; 207104 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Eric Syz, 1983-1984; 207105 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - S [2], 1982-1994; 207106 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - T [1], 1982-2002; 207107 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Chip Tom, 1983-1989; 207108 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - William Radawec, 1982-1985; 207109 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Lynda & Stewart Resnick, 1982-1990; 207110 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Anita Reiner, 1985-1986; 207111 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - R [1/2], 1994-2002; 207112 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - R [2/2], 1981-1994; 207113 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - [Doron Sabag], 1993; 207114 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Barbara & Eugene Schwartz, 1982-2003; 207115 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Ethel Scull, 1981-1983; 207116 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Stan Sehler, 1985-1986; 207117 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Mark Selwyn, 1985-1987; 207118 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - John Martin Shea, 1982-1983; 207119 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Steve Shane, 1987-2003; 207120 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - S [3] [1/3], 1991-2002; 207121 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - S [3] [2/3], 1979-1991; 207122 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - S [3] [3/3], 1981-2004; 207123 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - W. Wightman, 1996; 207124 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Donald Williams [Wallens], 1985-1986; 207125 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Ealan Wingate, 1983-1987; 207126 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - U/V [1/2], 1987-2002; 207127 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - U/V [2/2], 1982-1995; 207128 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Nelson Woo, 2000-2002; 207129 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - W, 1980-2002; 207130 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Celia Walker, 1982-1983; 207131 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Emy Weinstein, 1985; 207132 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Ulfert Wilke, 1984-1985; 207133 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - T [2], 1981-2001; 207134 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Bette Ziegler, 1981-1989; 207135 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Ora Zucker, 1979-1993; 207136 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Y-Z, 1980-2001; 207137 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Subseries B: Dealers, 204157
    Series comprises correspondence between the gallery and other art dealers and galleries, as well as other related documents.
    - A, 1982-2002; 207138 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - [Brooke Alexander], 1980-1983; 207139 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Art America '92, 1992; 207140 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Amelio, 1991-1996; 207141 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Contacts from Arco - Madrid; 1989, 1996; 207142 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Ambrosino Gallery, Miami, 1994-1996; 207143 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Salvatore Ala Gallery, 1982-1991; 207149 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Thomas Ammann Fine Art, 1979-1983; 207150 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Juana de Aizpura - Madrid, 1983-1992; 207151 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Asher/Faure Gallery, 1985-1988; 207152 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Attolico Roma, 1980-1991; 207153 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Vrej Baghoomian, 1989-1992; 207154 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Sergio Beraccini, 1989-2001; 207155 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - B, 1980-2002; 207156 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Bacardi Art Center, 1981-1985; 207157 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Baumgartner Galleries, 1992-1999; 207158 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Ramis Barquet, 1993-2002; 207159 (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - [Baker Gallery], 1981-1982; 207161 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Barbara Balkin Gallery, 1981-1984; 207162 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - [Ernst Beyeler Gallery], 1982-1995; 207163 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Blum Helman Gallery, 1982-1994; 207164 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Bishofberger, 1974-1996; 207165 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Mary Boone, 1980-1990; 207166 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Bentley Gallery (Arizona), 1996-1997; 207167 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - C, 1980-1999; 207168 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Ferideh Cadot, 1983-2000; 207169 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Cheim & Read, 1997; 207170 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - [Fabian Carlsson Gallery], 1983-1992; 207171 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Thomas Cohn, 1991-1995; 207172 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Leo Castelli, 1978-1991; 207173 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Cava Gallery, 1983-1986; 207174 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Kyoko Chirathivat, 1994-1999; 207175 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Christian Cheneau, 1985; 207176 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Jan Cicero Gallery, 1980; 207177 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1982-1987; 207178 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Diego Cortez, 1981-1996; 207179 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Chantal Crousel, 1981-1985; 207180 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Paolo Curti, 1991-2003; 207181 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - D, 1980-1995; 207182 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Isabella Del Frate, 1977-1995; 207183 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Luciana Duce; Helen Turner; Kim Turner, 1989-1990; 207184 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Galerie Di Meo, 1994; 207185 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Marianne Deson, 1979-1984; 207186 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Mario Diacono, 1981-1991; 207187 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Lois Dixon, 1982; 207188 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Anthony D'Offay, 1981-1991; 207189 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - E, 1986-2001; 207190 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Andre Emmerich Gallery, 1983; 207191 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Rosa Esman Gallery, 1983; 207193 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - F, 1978-2001; 207194 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Konrad Fischer, 1980-1981; 207195 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Galerie Six Friedrich, 1982-1996; 207196 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Eric Franck, 1978-1987; 207197 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Matthew Fraser [Prints] Chuck Connelly, 1988-1992; 207198 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Barbara Farber, 1981-1992; 207199 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - G, 1975-2002; 207200 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Galerie Barbel Grasslin, 1985; 207201 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Fuller Goldeen Gallery, 1983-1988; 207202 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Fay Gold Gallery, 1982-1991; 207203 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Foster Goldstrom Fine Arts, 1983; 207204 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Larry Gagosian, 1978-1990; 207205 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Greenberg Gallery, 1979-1986; 207206 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - [G], 1985, 1991; 207207 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Linda Farris Gallery, 1978; 207208 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Vivian Horan, 1978-1998; 207209 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Simmard & Halm Gallery, 1987; 207210 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Peta Harcus Gallery, 1980-1990; 207211 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Susanne Hilberry, 1981; 207212 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Rhona Hoffman Gallery, 1979-1987; 207213 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Hillman R. Holland, 1986; 207214 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Tod Hosfelt, 1996-1997; 207215 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - H [1/2], 1983-2002; 207216 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - H [2/2], 1978-1989; 207217 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - I/J, 1978-2000; 207289 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Akira Ikeda Gallery, 1981-1990; 207290 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Japan Galleries, 1982, 1986; 207291 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Janus Gallery, L.A., 1981-1985; 207292 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - [K], 1981-1993; 207293 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - K, 1993-2000; 207294 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - [L], 1984-2001; 207295 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Gordon Locksley, 1986-1995; 207296 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - L, 1979-1997; 207297 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Drs. Jhim Lamoree, 1985-1986; 207298 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Margo Leavin Gallery, 1979, 1986; 207299 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Jim Lodge, 1981-1986; 207300 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Galerie Lietzow, 1981-1990; 207301 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Nicolas Logsdail (Lisson Gallery), 1980-1984; 207302 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Roberta Lietti, 1992-1993; 207303 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - L.A. Louver, 1981-1991; 207304 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Luhring, 1985-1996; 207305 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Lumen Travo, 1996-1997; 207306 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Jan Eric Lowenadler, 1981-1990; 207307 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - M [1], 1982-2002; 207308 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - [Paul Maenz], undated; 207309 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - M [2], 1982-2000; 207310 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Chis Middendorf, 1982-1985; 207311 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Robert Miller Gallery, 1982-1983; 207312 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Namia Mondolfi, 1993-2000; 207313 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Moos, 1984-1988; 207314 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Noretta Malaguzzi, 1978-1994; 207315 (Box 18, Folder 27)